A Guide to the Impressed Property Claim Records of the Auditor of Public Accounts, 1776-1794
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1988-1994, 2006.
  - 1994, 2004 (Accession 43628)., 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board meeting, 2004 Jan 15. (Box 5)
    - Agency Head meeting, 2004. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Grown Conference and Trade Show, 2004 Jan 21-23. (Box 5)
    - Carolina/Virginia Dairy Products Association, 2004 Jan 27. (Box 5)
    - Virginia State Dairymen's Association - Meeting, 2004 Jan 20. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Soybean Association - Winter Conference, 2004 Feb 6. (Box 5)
    - Virginia State Feed Association - Annual Conference, 2004 Feb 25-26. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Cotton Economics - Annual Meeting, 2004 Feb 10. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Beef Industry Council - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 Feb 17. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Food and Beverage Association - Annual Meeting, 2004 Mar 15-16. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council - Board Meeting, 2004 Mar 22. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Wine Board Transition Task Force, 2004 Apr 6. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 Apr 8. (Box 5)
    - virginia Poultry Health and Management Seminar, 2004 Apr 13. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2004 Apr 15. (Box 5)
    - VEIAA - Meeting, 2004 Apr 29. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Small Grains Association - Field Day, 2004 May 20. (Box 5)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee - Meeting, 2004 May 12. (Box 5)
    - Forestry Expo, 2004 June 4. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Forage and Grassland Council - Conference, 2004 June 12-16. (Box 5)
    - VEIAA - Spring Conference, 2004 June 23. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2004 July 15. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Cattlemen Conference, 2004 July 16. (Box 5)
    - Emergency Support Work Group Training, 2004 July 8. (Box 5)
    - AG Expo - Eastern Shore, 2004 Aug 12. (Box 5)
    - State Fair of Virginia Wine Competition, 2004 Aug 16. (Box 5)
    - Harrisonburg AI Meeting, 2004 Aug 18. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Wine Board - Meeting, 2004 Aug 23. (Box 5)
    - Virginia State University - Agriculture Field Day, 2004 Aug 24. (Box 5)
    - UVLA Field Day, 2004 Sept 1. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 Sept 23. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2004 Oct 14. (Box 5)
    - VDACS Regional Service Awards, 2004. (Box 5)
    - Farmers Market System Operations - Meeting, 2004 Nov 9. (Box 5)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee - Meeting, 2004 Nov 3. (Box 5)
    - VEIAA - Fall Conference, 2004 Oct 27. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council - State Policy and Development Committee, 2004 Nov 12. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation - Annual meeting, 2004 Nov 29. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2004 Mar 18. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2004 June 10. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2004 Sep 24. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2004 Dec 9. (Box 5)
    - Scorecard - Governor's Management Standard Executive Agreement, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Secretary of Administration, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Racing Fuels Register, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Southern States, 2004. (Box 6)
    - State Fair, 2004. (Box 6)
    - States Ratification Committee, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Southeastern Virginia Farmers Market Coop, 2004. (Box 6)
    - State Police, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004-2006. (Box 6)
    - Strategic Plan, 2002-2004. (Box 6)
    - Task Force - Agriculture, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Task Force - Equine Study, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Task Force - Food Safety, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco - Burley Tobacco Warehouse, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco - Tobacco Trust Certification Board, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco - National Tobacco Grower Settlement Trust, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco - Minutes of the Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Treasury, Dept. of, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Syngenta Crop Protection, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia State University History Project - African American Contributions, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Tech, 2004. (Box 6)
    - USDA, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Results, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Works, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Legislative tracking, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Wine Board Transition Task Force - Governor's Wine Study Work Group, 2004. (Box 7)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA), 2004. (Box 7)
    - Southern Trade Association (SUSTA), 2004. (Box 7)
    - Vanderwoude, Hill and Hill v. VDACS, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Suggested Reponses, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Wine Board Reduction, 2004. (Box 7)
  - 2006 (Accession 44828)., 8 cu. ft. (8 boxes)
    - Weekly reports to the Secretary, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Blankenship, Donald (Deputy Commissioner), 2006 Nov-Dec. (Box 1)
    - Blankenship, Donald (Deputy Commissioner), 2006 Jan-Nov. (Box 1)
    - Memos (SMT), 2006. (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous - Commissioner's Office, 2006.
    - Miscellaneous - Administrative and Finance Services, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Adams, Sandra, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Harris, Larry, 2006.
    - Miscellaneous - Facility Management, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Halblieb, Craig, 2006 Sept-Dec.
    - Halblieb, Craig, 2006 June-Aug. (Box 1)
    - Halblieb, Craig, 2006 Jan-May. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance Office, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Kapelewski, Joseph - Finance Office, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Layman, Barbara, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Procurement, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Development Services, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Dickenson, William P., Jr., 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Animal and Food Industry Services, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Wilkes, Richard, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Dairy and Food Security, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Food Uniformity Act, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Office of Dairy and Foods, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Communications and Promotions, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Lidholm, Elaine, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee (CAAC), 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Protection, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Alvarez, Andy, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Office of Consumer Affairs, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 2006 Sept-Nov. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 2006 June-Oct. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 2006 Mar-June. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 2006 Jan-Mar. (Box 3)
    - Office of Plants and Pest Services, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Bee Keeping study, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Report on Weights and Measures Fees, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Office of Product and Industry Standards, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Butts, Donald, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resources Office, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Jackson, Karen E., 2006. (Box 3)
    - Audit - Seed Laboratory, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Martin, Jay - Internal Auditor, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Seward, Roy, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy Planning and Research, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Stewardship, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Giles, Perida, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Askew, Rebecca, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Division of Marketing, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Sleight, Thomas, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Office of International Marketing, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Accomplishments - Governor, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Accounts, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Agendas (SMT), 2006. (Box 3)
    - Agreement - Farmers Markets Nutrition Program, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Coop Agreement - VDACS and USDA, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Apple Board, Virginia, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Attorney General, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Audit FLSA, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Avian Influenza, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Awards Committee - VDACS, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Boll Weevil, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Boll -Weevil - Eradication Foundation, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Chipokes Plantation Farm Foundation, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Virginia Agricultural Foundation, 2006. (Box 3)
    - CVC, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Commonwealth Preparedness, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Comptroller's Office, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Consolidated Lab Services, Div. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Cooperative Coyote Damage Control Program Report, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Cotton Board, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Delegates, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Disaster, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Economic Impact of Agriculture Report, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Education, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Contacts, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Evacuation Plan, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - EPA, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Farm Bureau Federation, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Farmers Market Board, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Foundation for Virginia's Natural Resources Board, 2006. (Box 4)
    - FOIA, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Govenor's Office, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Grant awards, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Health, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Horse Center, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - House Bill 980, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Interior, U.S. Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Interstate Pest Control Compact, 2006. (Box 4)
    - VITA, 2006. (Box 4)
    - JLARC Study, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Katrina Analysis, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Land Use, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Mandates - Federal, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Organic Milk Study, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Milk Commission, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Mountain View Farms, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Moving Relocation Expenses, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Peanut Growers Association, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Performance Measures, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Plasticulture, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Referendum - Cotton, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Referendum on levy - equine feed, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Risk Management Division (DGS), 2006. (Box 4)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Senators, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Sole Source, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Solem, Christine (goat milk), 2006. (Box 4)
    - Soutern States, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Specialty Crop Block Grant Program, 2006. (Box 4)
    - State Police, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - State Fair, 2006. (Box 4)
    - State Ratification Committee, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Strategic Planning, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Strategic Plan, 2005-2006. (Box 4)
    - Taxation, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Telecommuting, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Tobacco, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - USDA, 2006 Oct-Dec. (Box 4)
    - Out of Country requests, 2006. (Box 5)
    - Telecommunications bill, 2006. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 Sept-Oct. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 July-Aug. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 May-June. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 March-April. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 Jan-Feb. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board - Meeting, 2006 Sept. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Food and Beverage Association Fall Education Conference, 2006 Sept. (Box 6)
    - Agiculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Agriculture Field Day, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Nursery and Landscape Association Field Day, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - State Fair - Virginia Wine Competition Luncheon, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agriculture Expo, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Virginia State Dairymen's Association Board - Meeting, 2006 July. (Box 6)
    - Hurricane Emergency Exercise, 2006 July. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2006 July. (Box 6)
    - Commercial Vegetable Production Field Day, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Northampton County Agriculture Tour, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Innovations in Government Conference, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board - Meeting, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Simply Fresh opening, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Service Board - Meeting, 2006 May. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Health and Management Seminar, 2006 Apr. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Beef Expo, 2006 Apr. (Box 6)
    - Seminar - Assist Producers in Marketing Virginia Meat Products, 2006 Mar. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council - Meeting, 2006 mar. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Animal ID Forum, 2006. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board - Meeting, 2006 Mar. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Wine Board - Meeting, 2006 Mar. (Box 6)
    - Emergency Management Celebration and Open House, 2006 Mar. (Box 6)
    - Emergency Operations Training, 2006 Feb. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Corn Growers Association and Virginia Soybean Association - Meeting, 2006 Feb. (Box 6)
    - VITA - Meeting, 2006 Feb. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Grown Conference, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Pork Conference, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Crop Production Association, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Dairymen's Association Board - Meeting, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Eastern Shore Agriculture Conference and Trade Show, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - AFIS, 2006. (Box 6)
    - CP, 2006. (Box 6)
    - CP Completed, 2006. (Box 6)
    - Marketing, 2006. (Box 6)
    - Marketing Completed, 2006. (Box 6)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 Sept-Oct. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 July-Aug. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 May-June. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 Mar-May. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 Feb-Mar. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 Jan. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006. (Box 7)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee - Meeting, 2006 May. (Box 7)
    - Post General Assembly Session Analysis and Review, 2006 May. (Box 7)
    - Public Service Week, 2006 May. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Arbor Day Ceremony, 2006 Apr. (Box 7)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2006 Apr. (Box 7)
    - Environment Virginia Symposium, 2006 Apr. (Box 7)
    - State Service Merit Awards Presentations, 2006. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Agribus Council - Meetings, 2006 Nov. (Box 7)
    - CMA-VEIAA - Meeting, 2006 Nov. (Box 7)
    - Tomatoes and Food Safety - Meeting, 2006 Nov. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Wine Appreciation Celebration, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Senate Committee on Agriculture, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Conservation of Natural Resources, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Emergency Management - AI Exercise, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Agriculture Summit, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Energy Conference, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - USDA, 2006 Jan-Sept. (Box 8)
    - U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service grant, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Veterans Services, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU), 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Executive Institute (VEI), 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Tech (VPISU), 2006. (Box 8)
    - Year End Closure, 2006. (Box 8)
    - YMCA, 2006. (Box 8)
    - NASDA, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Wine Board, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Suggested Responses, 2006 Sept-Dec. (Box 8)
    - Suggested Responses, 2006 May-Sept. (Box 8)
    - Suggested Responses, 2006 Jan-May. (Box 8)